{
    "subject": "resource/Jumex",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingDate",
    "object": "1961-04-27",
    "human_readable": "Jumex was founded on April 27th, 1961.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8662825226783752,
            "question": "When was Jumex founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8133904337882996,
            "question": "What is the significance of April 27th to Jumex?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013857007026672,
            "question": "Where was Jumex founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6394104361534119,
            "question": "Can you find any information about Jumex's founders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.621748685836792,
            "question": "In what month was Jumex established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5312869548797607,
            "question": "What year did Jumex begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28738850355148315,
            "question": "Is Jumex a relatively new company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27914959192276,
            "question": "How old is Jumex as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2697441279888153,
            "question": "What type of company is Jumex?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13166466355323792,
            "question": "What products or services does Jumex likely offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jumex was founded on April 27th, 1961.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7337_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Jumex?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7337_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Jumex as of today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7337_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jumex a relatively new company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7337_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7337_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Jumex was indeed founded on April 27th, 1961. There is no contradictory information provided in any of the files to suggest otherwise. Therefore, the statement is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided across multiple documents which all mention that Jumex was founded on April 27th, 1961."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}